<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Releases on KyberVPK</title>
    <link>https://kybervpk.fi/en/releases/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Releases on KyberVPK</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 21:00:00 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kybervpk.fi/en/releases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Checklist for victims of a data breach</title>
      <link>https://kybervpk.fi/en/releases/checklist-for-victims-of-a-data-breach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 21:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kybervpk.fi/en/releases/checklist-for-victims-of-a-data-breach/</guid>
      <description>We have collected a comprehensive list of notes especially for victims of the Vastaamo data breach. If you have been a client of Vastaamo before the year 2019, your confidential information might have been stolen. The list has been updated on 06.11.2020.
Based on current knowledge, Vastaamo&amp;rsquo;s client registry was breached in November 2018 and there has been a second smaller breach in 2019 before March 2019. According to Vastaamo, there is no indication that the whole database has been leaked in 2019 incident, but it is possible that information regarding some individuals has been copied.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Press Release 19.03.2020</title>
      <link>https://kybervpk.fi/en/releases/press_release_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kybervpk.fi/en/releases/press_release_1/</guid>
      <description>COVID-19 creates new threats - Finnish ethical hacker team helps healthcare companies with cyber challenges During the pandemic, an increasing number of cyber attacks have targeted healthcare organizations and others. The Finnish hacker collective KyberVPK was founded to help providers of critical services in the fight against cyber attacks and in recovering from them. KyberVPK - Community Cyber Response Force is a voluntary organization established to help health care providers and providers of other critical services address and prevent cyber threats.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>